[
  {
    "question": "abandon",
    "correct": "放棄"
  },
  {
    "question": "beneficial",
    "correct": "有益的"
  },
  {
    "question": "complex",
    "correct": "複雜的"
  },
  {
    "question": "derive",
    "correct": "獲得"
  },
  {
    "question": "efficient",
    "correct": "有效率的"
  },
  {
    "question": "fluctuate",
    "correct": "波動"
  },
  {
    "question": "generate",
    "correct": "產生"
  },
  {
    "question": "highlight",
    "correct": "強調"
  },
  {
    "question": "imply",
    "correct": "暗示"
  },
  {
    "question": "justify",
    "correct": "證明…是正當的"
  },
{
    "question": "knowledgeable",
    "correct": "博學的"
  },
  {
    "question": "leverage",
    "correct": "利用"
  },
  {
    "question": "modify",
    "correct": "修改"
  },
  {
    "question": "navigate",
    "correct": "導航"
  },
  {
    "question": "optimize",
    "correct": "優化"
  },
  {
    "question": "perceive",
    "correct": "感知"
  },
  {
    "question": "quantify",
    "correct": "量化"
  },
  {
    "question": "relevant",
    "correct": "相關的"
  },
  {
    "question": "sustain",
    "correct": "維持"
  },
  {
    "question": "transform",
    "correct": "轉變"
  },
{
    "question": "utilize",
    "correct": "利用"
  },
  {
    "question": "validate",
    "correct": "驗證"
  },
  {
    "question": "warrant",
    "correct": "保證"
  },
  {
    "question": "yield",
    "correct": "產出"
  }
]